{
    "subject": "Ann_Keen",
    "predicate": "isMarriedTo",
    "object": "Alan_Keen",
    "human_readable": "Ann Keen is married to Alan Keen.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9881938695907593,
            "question": "Is Alan Keen married to Ann Keen?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9672407507896423,
            "question": "Does Alan Keen have a spouse named Ann?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9591645002365112,
            "question": "Is Ann Keen's husband named Alan Keen?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9568261504173279,
            "question": "Who is Ann Keen married to?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.886348307132721,
            "question": "What is the relationship between Ann Keen and Alan Keen?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.850079357624054,
            "question": "Who are Ann and Alan Keen?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8350516557693481,
            "question": "What can you tell me about the relationship between Ann and Alan Keen?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8263281583786011,
            "question": "Who are Alan and Ann Keen related to?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8055020570755005,
            "question": "What is the name of Ann Keen's spouse?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.19396454095840454,
            "question": "Name one person married to another in this statement."
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Ann Keen is married to Alan Keen.",
            "html": "yago_4419_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the name of Ann Keen's spouse?",
            "html": "yago_4419_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Who are Alan and Ann Keen related to?",
            "html": "yago_4419_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What can you tell me about the relationship between Ann and Alan Keen?",
            "html": "yago_4419_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "yago_4419_100.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_4419_103.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_4419_19.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_4419_4.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_4419_42.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_4419_44.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_4419_52.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_4419_57.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_4419_60.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_4419_94.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'yes'} \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the answer in the form of a structured JSON format:\n\n```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe information in the documents supports the triple. The documents mention that Mr Keen and his wife Ann are mentioned together several times, and it is explicitly stated that he married Ann in 1980."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\nThe documents state that Mr. Keen and his wife Ann made headlines over their expenses claims, indicating they were a married couple. Additionally, it mentions that Ann Keen was the MP for Brentford and Isleworth until 2010, and that Alan Keen is survived by his wife Ann. This confirms that Ann Keen is indeed married to Alan Keen."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": "is true",
            "full_ans": "0.9"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": "is true",
            "full_ans": "0.9"
        }
    },
    "final_decision": "true",
    "actual_decision": "true",
    "analysis": {
        "error_category": "caafscd",
        "error_detail": "cdscsd",
        "category": "csdcs",
        "stratum": "fwefew",
        "topic": "wefw"
    }
}